IN THE NEAR FUTURE
THE SEA LEVEL RISES
DUE TO RAPID CLIMATE CHANGE
AND HUMANS DECIDE TO RELOCATE TO SPACE
SPACE
AFTER SUCCESSFULLY BUILDING SHELTERS
BETWEEN EARTH
AND THE MOON'S ORBITAL PLANES
THEY SPEND DECADES MIGRATING CITIZENS
TO THE 80 OR SO SHELTERS
SHELTERS
AS THE HUMANS SETTLE DOWN...
SHELTERS NO. 8, 12, AND 13
DECLARE THEMSELVES THE ADRIAN REPUBLIC
AND THEY BEGIN ATTACKING EARTH
AND OTHER SHELTERS INDISCRIMINATELY
ADRIAN REPUBLIC
THIS LEADS TO DECADES OF WAR
BETWEEN THE ALLIED FORCE
AND THE ADRIAN REPUBLIC
WAR
HUMANS LEFT ON EARTH CONTINUE
TO PRODUCE MUNITIONS
LIVING LIKE COGS
IN THE MACHINE THAT IS WAR
HUMANS
- Team 45, do you copy?
- It's Captain Yun Jung-yi.
Captain Yun, there was a nearby explosion.
Are you still alive?
How else would I answer you? Jeez.
What's your team's status?
Did you reach the fuel rod?
We're here,
but it's looking bleak.
What is that?
We were informed
that Adrian's new ZIMBO is there.
Damn, thanks for telling me so early.
This ZIMBO's energy battery
is in the rear.
Target that. Target the rear!
Backup will arrive soon.
As if I can wait...
I already checked that.
I told you to set it up right.
- Check the rail gun.
- Roger.
Man, she failed to escape
at the exact same point.
I know.
I'll send for a detailed lab analysis.
Yes, do that now.
Oh, you're here.
Man, what on earth is the problem?
But she sure is a legendary mercenary.
Look at how many robots she destroyed
getting to this point.
I know.
Maybe the enemy's programming
is poorly done.
I think we should start
with a different setup tomorrow.
Oh, no.
Hey, we can't tamper with that.
We must replicate the real circumstances
to better understand her brain map.
Wrap up for today.
We have important guests coming.
- Yes, Chief.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Here.
- Yes.
Let's get moving.
- Should I send this to Tech Support?
- Yes, that's right.
We'll finish things up before we go.
Okay.
Hold on.
This.
You sure this is fresh?
We just caught it.
I mean...
it has an awfully resentful expression.
Don't get all tensed up.
It's a joke. A joke.
I'm counting on you.
Okay, let's pick up the pace.
You know today is really important, right?
Oh, Chief, you're here.
Thank you for your hard work.
Director.
Is all this really necessary?
They're all elders.
Older people consider these things
more important than you'd think.
You aren't nervous, are you?
Slept well last night?
Yes.
Are you feeling okay, sir?
You look very nervous.
What... me?
Presentations require showmanship.
I'm focused on that. That's why.
Stiffly reading off a script
isn't a presentation.
You need to be humorous like me,
while serving great food and cocktails.
That's how we get unstinting support
for the company.
You get it, right?
Greetings, I'm Kra... ro...
Greetings, I'm Kronoid's... Lab Director,
Kim Sang-hoon.
Shall we start?
Year 2135.
The rising sea level
and depletion of resources
led mankind
to look for new ways to survive.
And we found new opportunities
in the shelters built in space.
But shortly after,
Space Shelters no. 8, 12, and 13
declared themselves the Adrian Republic,
starting a civil war, threatening Earth
and the rest of the shelters.
I narrated this myself.
This war between the Allied Force
and the Adrian Republic
has been ongoing for the last 40 years.
I also directed the music and everything.
The AI-developing Kronoid Lab
was founded in the year 2130 CE,
with top-notch researchers
and cutting-edge...
We all know this. Skip to the point.
Oh...
Hey, fast-forward!
Adrian Civil War's legendary mercenary,
the pride of Korea,
she's Captain Yun Jung-yi.
The leader of Squadron 8 Team 45,
Captain Yun Jung-yi
partook in countless missions
and achieved great results.
Shall we skip over the stuff we know?
Thirty-five years ago, Captain Yun
joined the bombing operation
of a fuel rod in Adrian's Shelter B-25,
but the mission was a failure,
and she ended up in a coma.
With permission from her bereaved family,
Kronoid has spared nothing
for her recovery,
copying her brain
and converting it into data.
With all her tactical knowledge,
combat skills,
as well as her strong loyalty
and determination,
we will develop
the greatest AI to command combat.
Right.
We plan to name this
the "JUNG_E" program.
This was created
so Captain Yun's spirit would live on.
Oh, and Captain Yun's...
Her daughter, Dr. Yun Seo-hyun,
plans to finalize the project
as the team lead.
Shall we discuss this further with her?
Chief!
Don't be nervous, okay?
This is the replicated data
from Ms. Yun's brain.
We are developing an AI
that focuses on reflecting
her combat skills and experience,
based on her replicated brain data
from her final mission.
Just like now,
whenever the android uploaded
with her brain data does something,
her behavioral pattern
is marked like this.
This part here
shows the strongest reaction
when in combat.
Shall we mark that part in green?
Since our projects are always green-lit.
Ding, ding!
Having fun?
It was a joke.
We're going to use these simulations
to extract and develop
only the combat-related data
from Ms. Yun's brain data,
and create the greatest combat AI.
So,
did the robot manage to escape?
Not yet.
All of this sounds good,
but if she had succeeded
in the final mission,
the war would already be over.
That failure is why the Adrian Civil War
is still ongoing after 40 years.
The Korean mercenary...
She was popular back then.
But now, many people think
that Yun Jung-yi is the reason
the war has been dragging on.
Oh, what a heated debate!
But our combat AI is different.
We're making every effort
to extract only her
combatting strengths...
Then why does it keep failing
to escape from the same simulation?
Why would you develop a combat AI
using the brain of a soldier
who failed her mission?
She...
will escape.
We will make sure
Capt. Yun Jung-yi escapes that simulation.
Plus,
we'll make her a lasting hero
of the Allied Force.
That's by a famous artist.
It's the Yun Jung-yi edition.
Great, huh?
The sunset looks great, too.
Wow, it arrived already.
Adorable, no?
I heard people in the old days
focused on a product's design
over its practicality.
Sure, everything was abundant back then.
Right.
Your vehemence at the end!
It moved me, really!
Those old fogies went silent.
They secretly told me
that we can start supplying
once the AI passes the simulation test.
That's good.
Take a seat.
Would you like coffee?
The taste of the 20th century.
No, thank you.
I have to interview number 17
before termination.
Oh, the interview.
Do we really need to do that
before terminations?
Chief.
Does it help with understanding
the brain map?
Well, the more accurately
we understand it, the better.
You're happy, right?
The company's signature product,
which just might end this war,
being launched in your mother's name.
All thanks to the chairman.
The chairman is a great man.
You've known him longer than I have.
I've only worked for him
for a little over ten years.
You met him when you were young
because of your mother.
It's more like he's taken care of me
since I was young.
Now that the "JUNG_E" project is back on,
forget about what that old fart said.
Captain Yun was
a globally popular soldier.
And yet, he picks on one measly failure.
She's popular, that's why. He's jealous.
Your mother's still alive,
all thanks to our chairman.
Also, he seems to have high hopes
for this project.
I really, truly, really...
I'm counting on you, Chief.
Don't worry.
It's time for the interview.
I'll have to excuse myself.
Oh, yes, of course.
The chairman will be visiting soon,
so let's keep up the good work!
ACTIVATE
Hello, Ms. Yun?
Ms. Yun, pull yourself together.
Ms. Yun, can you hear me?
Is the mic on?
I think she can hear me fine. Ms. Yun!
Uh...
BRAIN MAP SENSORY CONTROL
PAIN LEVEL DECREASING
Okay, how's that?
The pain is bearable now, right?
Now let's calm down and talk...
What's this? I can't feel my body.
Come on, try to calm down...
Where am I?
Who are you? Did you do this to me?
Let me go!
What the hell have you done to me,
you bastards?
I can't get through to her.
I'm going to kill all of you bastards!
Interview over. Terminate number 17.
It seems like such a waste
to discard them every time.
You did well,
considering it's your first time.
Oh, well, I didn't really do much.
I heard you wanted to transfer
to our team from HQ.
Oh, yes.
I'm actually a fan of Captain Yun.
She was more popular than superheroes
when I was young.
Superheroes?
My mother actually
kept fighting in the war
because of me.
Sorry?
When I was young,
I had a tumor in my lungs.
The treatment cost a fortune.
The only way...
my mother could make that much money
was to become a mercenary.
I always worried
my mother might die because of me,
and I lived in fear
as I watched her head into battles.
The day I got the surgery
was the last day she went to fight.
I always wondered...
"Mom never got to live her life
because of me."
"Did she ever resent me?"
Then why not ask her?
Sorry?
You can ask those things.
When you're done with a test,
ask one in an interview.
If it ever resented its daughter.
Sure.
- I could do that.
- Right.
Anyway, I have the ethics test today.
Jae-kyung, please finish up
no. 17's interview report.
Oh, the ethics test... Yes, ma'am.
Uh, ma'am. Thank you for the story.
I'm such a big fan of Yun Jung-yi.
Even those backstories are fun.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Oh, you came again.
Mom, you'll come soon, right?
Of course,
be a good girl when you get there, okay?
Don't cry, it's nothing.
Alright? Don't cry.
It's not like you won't see me again.
Okay?
Seo-hyun.
I have to go on another mission.
So, Mommy can't be with you
when you have the surgery.
But you'll be okay without me, right?
My daughter is a brave girl, right?
Mom.
And when I'm done?
Will you be there after the surgery?
Of course.
I'm planning to finish this mission
real quick.
I'll be right by your side
after your surgery, okay?
Honey, give me a lucky cheek rub.
Come here.
Ah, there's my girl.
Rub!
She'll be going in now.
I'll see you soon. You can do it. Okay?
This is the eighth ethics test
of Kronoid Lab's Chief Yun Seo-hyun.
Ms. Yun, have you ever had a pet?
No.
Have you ever felt attached to a product
or an object?
Yes.
Have you ever named the object?
Have you ever written three or more lines
of poetry while watching the sunset?
Yes.
Have you ever bought
an original piece of artwork at a price
that feels too expensive for your means?
No.
The test results will be sent
to the company in two to three days.
But above all, the scan results show
that the cancer cells are spreading
from your previous surgery area.
Ms. Yun, as I've told you before,
cancer has spread past your lungs
to all your other organs.
Surgery is impossible at this point.
If this was inevitable,
I guess the surgery was all for nothing.
Pardon?
It's nothing.
So...
how long do I have left?
Three months at most.
All we can suggest right now
is that you copy your brain,
and switch over to a prosthetic body.
These days, the law guarantees
equal human rights
to those who copy their brains
and switch to prosthetic bodies.
Of course, the price might be an issue...
What if...
I can't afford it?
If Type A is beyond your means,
where you switch to a prosthetic body
using a brain replication system
with guaranteed equal human rights,
I recommend type B,
which limits basic human rights
such as marriage, residential mobility,
and child adoption.
Also, you'll have to consent
to provide your brain data
to government agencies.
If you still find that to be costly,
there is Type C...
You don't get treated as a human being
with Type C.
Well, it's not as bad as you think.
But your brain data
will be provided to certified companies
or those that purchase it,
and they will be making
countless clones with it,
so you won't be recognized
as your own person. No.
But as you know,
Type C costs nothing at all.
Rather, a subsidy is provided
to the bereaved.
Your mother, Captain Yun Jung-yi,
was also contracted
for Type C with Kronoid.
I'll think about it.
Seeing as I'm already here,
I'd like to see my mother.
Sure, okay then.
Give me a call
after you've thought about it.
All right.
Ms. Yun barely survived,
but she is currently unconscious.
If you consent to Type C brain replication
before her cerebral cortex is damaged,
we can avoid brain death.
If you sign the agreement now,
we'll take care of Ms. Yun's treatment,
and her daughter's education fees
and living expenses.
Please read it carefully before you sign.
Poor thing...
Ms. Yun's brain data will be
developed into a product
that will end this tedious war.
We'll relay your decision to the company
and proceed accordingly.
The living expenses will be sent shortly...
Hi Seo-hyun.
I brought a present for you.
Your mom will become an eternal hero.
You'd like that, right?
COPYING BRAIN REPLICATION DATA
NO. 18 READY
No. 18 is good to go.
Do we have access?
Yes, we have a good signal.
No. 18 is in place.
- Min-jae.
- Yes, ma'am.
Check on Labs A, B, and C.
Yes, ma'am.
All figures look good.
Docking complete.
Okay.
I'll prepare the test.
Wait.
Let's start a little differently today.
Let's shoot its leg.
Hurry. Come on.
RAIL GUN CONTROLS
FIRE
The research isn't going anywhere
because we repeat the same simulation.
Now, I'd appreciate it if you could begin.
PAIN LEVEL INCREASING
It's the area that reacted
when no. 17 was shot.
It definitely reacts to pain.
Mark that in red...
Like a traffic light.
It's a joke. A joke.
Traffic light, my ass.
PAIN LEVEL INCREASING
Green light.
Let's go.
WILL TO FIGHT DECREASING
PAIN LEVEL INCREASING
Her will to fight is faltering.
The simulation will end soon.
Ugh, how boring.
Huh? Wait.
UNIDENTIFIED AREA INCREASING
Huh? What's that?
- Which area lit up?
- I'll check.
Its mobility is higher
than the green brainwave signal.
It's an unfamiliar area.
Hey, no!
You can't shoot the head.
Damn it.
- Go in and retrieve it now!
- Yes, sir.
- Replay the scene.
Hey, which part was it?
I'll check.
UNIDENTIFIED AREA INCREASING
This hasn't been activated before.
Oh, what could that be?
From what I see,
that's the key to building combat AIs.
Mark that area in... in yellow.
Answer me!
Yes, sir.
UNIDENTIFIED AREA INCREASING
Okay.
Let's put in some more effort.
We're briefing at HQ tomorrow.
Kronoid... Kronoid's Lab Director.
Hello, I'm Kronoid's Lab Director,
Kim Sang-hoon.
Has the chairman arrived?
I'll check.
The chairman isn't coming today.
Hello, Director Kim.
We haven't met.
I'm Managing Director Lee Se-yeon,
newly joining product development.
Okay.
The chairman isn't coming today?
He's being debriefed on our results.
I'm sure he's coming.
The chairman told me
to attend the presentation on his behalf
and relay it to him.
He told you that?
You're with product development?
I'm Managing Director Lee Se-yeon.
I've just been appointed to...
Anybody heard of product development?
Kronoid is a military AI development firm.
What is meant by product development?
How fun.
Can't hide feelings, just like him!
What?
Anyway, the chairman can't come today
due to a prior engagement.
So I'll be debriefed instead.
The chairman will visit the lab soon,
so you can take easy today, okay?
Those rude bastards.
After all the chairman's investments
put into developing combat AIs,
they're cutting back
on weapons development?
They have no clue about his dreams...
Right?
That clueless asshole...
She knows nothing
about what the chairman wants.
She's completely clueless.
This turned out so cool, right?
Yes, it's a marked upgrade
from the previous test body.
Where are we
on the AI we'll be uploading here?
We're done with the test version.
We must test it, of course.
I'm so excited!
Director!
The chairman's here. Will you go now?
Oh, really? Let's hurry.
Oh, can I take one of these?
Chairman would love to see this.
Oh, yes, of course.
Chief.
Oh, Chief.
When did you last take the ethics test?
The ethics test?
You know, the test
that identifies humans from AIs.
I took it recently.
I never skip them.
The chairman was asking.
Yun Jung-yi was your mother after all,
so he must be worried.
He's so thorough
and has plans for everything, so...
Surprise!
Hello, Chairman.
Thank you for making a visit to our lab.
I came to see if Director Kim
is operating well.
Plus, I need to talk to you.
The combat AI project is on track.
We just need to verify unverified sectors
and then we can begin testing...
Oh, I know about the combat AIs.
The combat AI you handed over
were further developed
by the researchers at HQ.
Oh...
We'll try harder with our research, too.
Seo-hyun.
You don't have to try so hard now.
- Pardon?
- The age of weapons production is over.
The Adrian Civil War is coming to an end.
The Allied Force reached an agreement
with the Adrian Republic.
Even munitions companies in the past
made thermoses
with their technology when wars ended.
I think it's our turn now.
I'm not saying
that our research was meaningless.
The brain replication AI research
allowed this company to branch out.
Combat AIs?
Now it's all nonsense.
We need to develop housekeeper
or service worker AIs now.
Let's see.
Did Captain Yun have any skills
other than throwing punches?
Sir.
So, you want the project to...
Yes, put a timely end to it.
Frustrated, aren't you?
I know how you feel.
I, too, was obsessed
with brain replication.
Rich people like me find
the most interest in such things.
When brain replication became
a possibility,
the first thing I thought was,
"Wow, I'll be able to live forever now."
That's what I thought.
So my first experiment was
to replicate my brain
and make an immortal version of myself.
That was the goal.
That's why the first robot I built...
was Sang-hoon here.
But the thing is,
I could've just died
because I'd replicated my brain,
but I couldn't.
Do you know why?
This prick right here... This thing...
It doesn't feel like me.
Because it isn't.
It's just something you rig up
to use like one of your limbs.
Right...
Say you record your mother's voice
on your rice cooker.
"Darling, the rice is cooked.
Come and eat."
That won't make it taste
like the rice your mother cooked.
Huh?
Isn't it funny?
It's a joke. A joke.
Sir.
Please let me finish
my mother's project properly.
Stop it.
We should wrap it up now.
When this project is over,
switch over to household android AIs.
I'll tell Sang-hoon that, too.
He'll be distressed.
He's not the type
to easily admit to failure.
I know that better than anyone.
Be nice to him,
even if he acts a bit snappy.
After this project wraps up,
I'll dispose of him anyway.
Let me talk to Sang-hoon now.
All right?
Seo-hyun, you need to stop obsessing.
...and has plans for...
Gosh, sir, when did you get here?
Did you walk out of your portrait?
Oh, Sang-hoon!
Your sense of humor is really
the best in the world!
You can go now.
But you came to see her...
Oh, I saw her. That's good enough.
Hey, stop making me laugh. Let's talk.
Yes, sir.
Look at this here...
Yes, well done.
Why?
Why can't she ever escape from there? Why?
Was the newly activated area
active this time?
No.
It hasn't been activated since then.
Why can't you find anything
after all these tries?
With our current technology,
it requires an immense amount of time
to study all areas of the brain.
Chief.
Are you satisfied
with the current combat AI?
Director...
Actually, HQ is satisfied
with what we have so far.
I'm not satisfied. I'm not satisfied!
Don't you know that HQ is trying
to wrap up our project?
They're disappointed, and yet,
you want to leave it half-done like this?
Bring no. 22 to Termination Advisory.
I must confirm the activated area
no matter what.
Keep its arms and legs intact.
Yes, sir.
Seriously, jeez...
Hello, sir.
Suspend motor functions.
Oh, yes.
- Hello, everyone.
- Yes.
Activate it.
Okay.
PAIN LEVEL INCREASING
Who are you all?
Who are you people?
Cut its arm off.
Sorry?
The arm?
Can't you hear me?
Cut its arm off, its arm.
Arm!
Right. Yes, sir.
Who are you people? What is this?
PAIN LEVEL INCREASING
The yellow area. Is it not reacting?
There's no reaction so far.
Was it shot on the left side back then?
Yes.
Who the hell are you, basta...
Activate it again.
It's not activating.
What?
I'm the administrator now.
No one can touch her.
Quick, activate it.
- I won't.
- Do it now, ma'am!
Direc...
The chairman says you should come into HQ.
Ma'am, are you okay?
I think he's gone crazy.
Jeez, that damn lunatic.
Listen, everyone.
Go organize the data we have so far,
and wrap up the combat AI project.
As for the data,
send it all to me.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Okay.
TEST MODEL DATA LIST
JUNG_E NO. 5, NO. 6, NO. 7...
BRAIN REPLICATION DATA MANAGEMENT
EXPORTED
JAE-KYUNG
Ma'am.
The brain data was copied and exported.
Oh, that's...
Yes, I...
brought it here for a little examination.
Ma'am!
Oh... ma'am!
Wait.
Ma'am!
Ma'am.
Please don't get the wrong idea.
I wasn't doing this for personal reasons...
You bastard!
Ma'am, please calm down and listen to me.
Not for personal reasons?
No, it was HQ!
HQ is proceeding with...
No, developing a new Captain Yun product,
and I was testing it.
I'm telling the truth.
A new product?
Yes, well, she was like
a celebrity war hero, you know.
We saw value in... using it for sexual use...
It has the potential to be developed
into a high-value product,
don't you think?
She... she was really popular!
The bereaved gave their permission, no?
Type C!
The product can be used for anything!
Ma'am.
HQ says,
the simulations will end tomorrow.
This is it.
They said our combat AI
was a pilot project.
What'd they say?
They said they'll begin new projects.
Household AIs and such.
The chairman...
Do you think he's disappointed in me?
PAIN LEVEL DECREASING
Captain Yun.
Are you awake?
Where am I?
Captain Yun.
Listen closely.
You have been...
extremely tortured by your enemy.
So what's my current condition?
I can't feel my body.
I can't see, either.
We barely managed to rescue you,
but you were severely tortured.
So you will die soon.
Soon, you will pass,
like you're falling asleep.
Please...
pass in peace.
END
Excuse me.
Hey, wait.
UNIDENTIFIED AREA INCREASING
Could you find out one thing for me?
Sure.
My daughter... had surgery today.
Did it go well?
UNIDENTIFIED AREA INCREASING
I really wanted to be there for her
after her surgery.
It went well.
Her surgery...
went well.
Really?
Oh, that's a relief.
That's great, really. I'm so glad.
Earlier today,
my daughter gave me a doll
before she went into surgery.
Tiny and adorable, just like her.
She gave it to me to give me strength,
and said...
This is going to protect you.
I made a wish on it.
Wow.
Thank you.
I'll keep this on me at all times.
But I lost it today while on the move,
so I felt bad about it this whole time.
She told me not to lose it.
Oh! Chief.
Yes. Today's the last day,
so I'll wrap things up.
Yes, ma'am.
ADMINISTRATOR - SEO-HYUN
UNIDENTIFIED AREA
DELETING
DELETING UNIDENTIFIED AREA
Captain Yun, can you hear me?
You'll probably think
that you're hearing my voice in a dream,
but this isn't a dream.
From now on,
listen closely.
You...
will be left in a coma
after a battle that's about to take place.
People will replicate your brain
and use the data
to make AIs like yourself...
You're here.
Docking complete.
Start if you're ready.
All right, we're starting.
WILL TO FIGHT INCREASING
The end.
Okay, everyone.
Thank you for all your work.
Undocking.
Sir.
The results look odd today.
The brain response
is much weaker than before.
I guess Captain Yun
was a weak-minded person.
Good work. Hope we cross paths again.
The chairman put in so much work.
Those evil bastards know nothing
about what he wants.
Thirty percent complete.
Huh? The director's back.
Hey, replay that part from before.
Okay.
Stop. Zoom in on the head.
Slow down...
Look closely.
She wasn't hit.
Sound the alarm.
The emergency alarm is activated.
All personnel, move quickly
into the panic room.
- What's this alarm? What's going on?
- This never happens, right?
All facilities will be shut down shortly.
- Min-jae, tell me when it's located.
- Okay.
Are the police on the move?
Yes, the alarm should have sent a signal.
How long will they take?
About five minutes.
That's more than enough time to escape.
Let's test the combat AIs.
CONNECT TO MAIN SERVER?
YES
DELETE ORIGINAL DATA OF YUN JUNG-YI?
DELETE
DELETING ORIGINAL DATA
Arrived at mission area. Begin operation.
Captain Yun!
Remember my voice?
The one from your dream.
I'm here to help.
Approaching striking point.
Begin entry, begin search.
Target eliminated.
One injured person found.
Emergency support required.
Target to be retrieved. Over.
They'll catch up soon.
Kronoid train no. 08 has arrived.
The door is opening.
Run
as far as you can.
Chief Yun Seo-hyun.
That ethics test you said you took.
Which company ran it?
Director.
Chief.
The chairman cared for you so much.
How can you let him down like this?
Don't move or your daughter dies!
I erased the memories about her daughter.
What?
Why?
Captain Yun Jung-yi is free now.
Well...
I see.
Wh... what is this?
You're just
the chairman's toy.
Is this... a joke?
Civilian detected.
The bullet went through.
I'll stop the bleeding.
The...
The police will arrive soon.
You need to run!
What about you?
I'll take care of myself.
Don't worry.
Don't worry about me anymore.
What you said...
Please...
Please, just go.
Live only for yourself.
Be free.
Please...
Please.
Go...
Now!
May all the luck...
in this world be with you.